<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Advanced Projects on</title><link>/docs/advanced-projects/</link><description>Recent content in Advanced Projects on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/docs/advanced-projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Wi-Fi Sniffing</title><link>/docs/advanced-projects/wi-fi-sniffing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>/docs/advanced-projects/wi-fi-sniffing/</guid><description>⛔️ Warning: This will erase your current USB Nugget installation, and you'll need to update your USB Nugget again before using it as a USB attack platform. The USB Nugget hardware can sniff Wi-Fi packets, allowing hackers to hunt for particular Wi-Fi devices or write packet filters to display deauthentication packets. To get started, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to install CircuitPython on your Nugget, as shown here. After installing CircuitPython, you can check out the guide below to start parsing Wi-Fi packets on your Nugget:</description></item><item><title>SSDP Phishing</title><link>/docs/advanced-projects/ssdp-phising/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>/docs/advanced-projects/ssdp-phising/</guid><description>⛔️ Warning: This will erase your current USB Nugget installation, and you'll need to update your USB Nugget again before using it as a USB attack platform The USB Nugget can be flashed to act as a SSDP (Simple Service Discovery Protocol) device, connecting to a Wi-Fi network appearing to nearby Windows users as a network-attached drive. This attack can be used to redirect users to phishing pages when they click on the drive.</description></item><item><title>Damn Vulnerable Nugget</title><link>/docs/advanced-projects/damn-vulnerable-nugget/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>/docs/advanced-projects/damn-vulnerable-nugget/</guid><description>⛔️ Warning: This will erase your current USB Nugget installation, and you'll need to update your USB Nugget again before using it as a USB attack platform Your USB Nugget can act as a vulnerable web application, letting you safely and legally practice webapp pentesting tools like Owasp Zap or Burpsuite! Check out the project here: https://github.com/RetiaLLC/DamnVulnerableNug To follow along, watch the video below:</description></item></channel></rss>